Guide to the William J. Gaughan Collection, 1887-2000 (Bulk 1940-1980) AIS.1994.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
William J. Gaughan Collection
1887-2000
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Gaughan, William J.
AIS.1994.03
30 Linear Feet (7 cartons of documents, 21,000 photographic negatives, 3,000 photographic prints, 24 motion picture films, 70 architectural drawings and blue prints, and 33 miscellaneous maps and oversize ephemera)
The William J. Gaughan Collection consists of documents, photographic prints and negatives, motion picture films, architectural drawings, and maps that chronicle operations and institutional history of the Homestead Steel Works, a mill owned by The Carnegie Steel Company and later the U.S. Steel Corporation. An employee of the Homestead Works for 36 year, William J. Gaughan, assembled the collection. Digital reproductions of selected photographic images are available online.
Biography
William J. Gaughan began employment at the United States Steel Homestead Works in 1947 as a laborer at open hearth furnace number four. He worked turns for two years at Homestead before obtaining his degree at Duquesne University. A year before his graduation, Gaughan became an observer in the metallurgical department.
Mr. Gaughan gained extensive management experience in the metallurgical division before becoming a Senior Designer of Operations Planning and Control in 1967. This group developed operations-oriented computer systems. He held this position until retirement in 1983.
Mr. Gaughan became interested in the history of the Homestead Works as a management trainee in the 1950s, when he heard a lecture on the 1892 Homestead Steel Strike. He began to make an extensive effort to preserve the history of steel in Homestead by collecting photographs and other items of historical significance.
Arrangement
The records are organized in the following fourteen series:
Series I. General History (1891-c2000)
Series II. Armor Production (1887-1961)
Series III. Computerized Control Systems (1958-1983)
Series IV. Steel Production and Plant Operations (1935-1981)
Series V. Management (c1930-1983)
Series VI. Binders, Bound Materials, and Publications (c1940-c1990)
Series VII. Miscellaneous, 1999 addition
Series VIII. Maps, Plans and Charts (1903-c1970)
Series IX. Negatives (1941-c1974)
Series X. Photographic Prints (c1890-c1980)
Series XI. Motion Picture Films (c1956-c1974)
Series XII. Oversize Prints, Architectural Drawings, Blueprints, and Miscellaneous (c1890-c1970)
Series XIII. Personal (c1942-c1999)
Scope and Content Notes
The William J. Gaughan Collection consists of records of the Carnegie Steel Company / U.S. Steel Corporation, but the majority of the material in this collection specifically relates to activities at the Homestead Works. The records date from the early years of the mill (1887) to the closing of the Homestead Works Plant in 1988 and include plant operational floor plans and architectural drawings of plant buildings and machinery, company publications, reports, internal memoranda, negatives, photographic prints, and motion picture film.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
William J. Gaughan donated this collection to the Archives Service Center in May 1994. Additonal material was donated in 1999 by Mr. Gaughan and in 2010 by his son, Jerry Gaughan.
Previous Citation
William J. Gaughan Collection, AIS.1994.03, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of the collection are available electronically at http://historicpittsburgh.org/collection/william-j-gaughan-collection.
Steel-works -- Pennsylvania -- Homestead; Labor; Iron and steel workers -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Steel industry and trade -- Pennsylvania -- Homestead; Steel industry and trade -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Homestead (Pa.) -- History; Iron and steel workers -- Pennsylvania -- Homestead.; Transportation; Steel-works -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Carnegie Steel Company; Homestead Steel Works; United States Steel Corporation
- General History, 1891-ca. 1980; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains a number of secondary sources about the history of Carnegie Steel Company and its Edgar Thomson, Duquesne, and Homestead plants. These sources include articles, academic papers, biographies, dissertations, and timelines describing the evolution of Pittsburgh's steel industry, leaders such as Andrew Carnegie and Charles Schwab, notable events like the Homestead Strike of 1892, and the chronology of ownership of the Homestead Works. This series also contains programs and memorabilia from public tours of the Homestead and Edgar Thomson Works. These tours focused on the history of the plants and the history of the steel making processes. This series also includes a United States Steel Gold bond and information regarding the Irvin Case looked into by the Truman Committee Investigation. The General History series also includes a quantity of primary source material from the early years of The Carnegie Steel Company such as correspondence, annual reports, check rolls, safety regulation booklets, and production statistics. Later material includes agreements between Carnegie Steel / U.S. Steel and unions (1934-1977), a warning to management about "Summer Work-In" student agitators (1960s), and various memorabilia dating from the World War II era until the 1980s.
  An addition of materials were made to this collection and added on to this series.
  - Secondary Sources, 1.
    - Articles, essays and papers about the history of the Edgar Thomson Works (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Articles, essays and papers about the history of the Carnegie Steel Company (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Articles, essays and papers about the history of the Duquesne Works (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition catalog and excerpts from books about Homestead History (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - National Park Service, Homestead Steel Works and Carrie Furnaces Homestead, Pennsylvania: Inventory of Historic Structures and Their Significance (Draft) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Short histories, articles and exhibition catalogs about Homestead Works (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Investigation into employment of Pinkerton Service during strike of 1892. U.S. House Reports vol. 3. No. 2447-2621, 1892-1893. (copy) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Homestead Strike of 1892, Dissertation by J. Bernard Hogy of University of Chicago, 1943 (photocopy from microfilm) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Chronologies of Edgar Thomson and Homestead Works (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Short Biographies of Andrew Carnegie; Ralph H. Watson, Vice President of U.S. Steel 1930-1946; Charles M. Schwab; and William J. Gaughan (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Statistics about African-American Employment 1910-1920 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Dispatch (Articles about Homestead Strike), July 12, 1892 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings about history of Pittsburgh steelmaking (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Steel Mill Tours, 2.
    - Program from Edgar Thomson Works Public Visiting Day, October 1936 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Materials from Homestead Works Open House, October 15-17, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Materials from International Visitors Tour, August 7, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Materials from Secondary Century of Steel Making Tour, April 24, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Materials from Cub Scout Tour, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Early Primary Sources and Homestead Works Memorabilia, 3.
    - Pamphlets, booklets and programs from U.S. Steel, Carnegie Steel and Homestead Works for events, public relations, and industrial concerns, 1900-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Pamphlets, booklets and programs from U.S Steel, Carnegie Steel and Homestead Works for events, public relations and industrial concerns, 1900-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous management correspondence, Carnegie Steel Company, 1891-1901 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Private Code for Use of the Carnegie Steel Company, Limited, and its Partners and Agents, November 1896 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - First Annual Report of the United States Steel Corporation (copy), 1902 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Carnegie Steel Company, Employee Check Roll, Edgar Thomson Furnaces, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Carnegie Veteran Association, 1902 and Obituaries of Early members (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Rules, Regulations and Instructions Governing Safety Bureau, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie Steel Company General Instructions to Employees to Avoid Accidents, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Homestead Works Telephone Directories, 1917 and 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Production statistics, ca. 1890s and 1912 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Company life insurance, certificate and correspondence (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Descriptions and Specifications of Hydraulic Forging Press, 1890s (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Register of triennial assessments of Pittsburgh iron mills, 1865-1867 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - "Personnel Reallocation: Edgar Thomson Works", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Agreements between Carnegie Steel Co. and the CIO, 1941-1949 (and 1934) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Agreements between U.S. Steel Co. and the USWA, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Handbook of Terms Commonly Used in Steel and Nonferrous Industries, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Production and Performance Report from Homestead District Works, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - "Talk Piece to be Uses in Connection with Acquainting Members of Management with Problems of 'Summer Work-in,'", 1960s (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Pamphlets about production and products from Alan Wood Steel Company, Coshohocken, PA (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Copy of U.S. Steel Corporation Gold Bond, ca. 1920 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Copy of Medal Issued to National Guard during 1892 Strike (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous memorabilia from Pittsburgh steel industry (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous World War II memorabilia from Homestead Works (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous notes and papers from office of William J. Gaughan (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Materials from collection duplicated and mounted for 1995 exhibit (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Production statistics 140" mill, 1905 (Box 2, Volume 1)
  - Topical, 4.
    - History of Homestead (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    - Homestead Business (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Battle of Homestead Foundation (Box 40, Folder 5-7)
    - Order Forms, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Metallurgical Department (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - General Plan Layout-History of Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation Plants Pittsburgh District (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Walsh Bridge (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Duquesne Works (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Clairton Coke Works (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Mon Valley (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Management Club, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Founders of the Superintendant Club (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Irvin case/Truman Committee Investigation, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Monongahela Morning- Draft Proposal (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - United States Steel Gold Bond (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Armor Production, 1887-1961; II.
  The Armor Production Series contains material documenting the production, testing, and sale of armor at the Homestead Works, with the majority of documents pertaining to armor production for military use during World War II. Files in this series include reports about metallurgy tests from 1894 and 1912; government publications and studies from World War I and World War II; and correspondence between Homestead management and the U.S. Armed Forces during World War II.
  - Government reports, circulars and statements about armor production, 1887-1904 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reports on armor experiments and testing at Homestead Metallurgical Department, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reports on armor experiments and testing at Homestead Metallurgical Department, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Reports on armor experiments and testing at Homestead Metallurgical Department, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reports on armor experiments and testing at Homestead Metallurgical Department, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
  - Reports on armor (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Record of armor orders, 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A Study of Light Armor Plate Production for Aircraft Use, Sections A-C, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Study of Light Armor Plate Production for Aircraft Use, Sections D-G, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - A Study of Light Armor Plate Production for Aircraft Use, Sections H-J, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Reports from Aricraft Armor and Helmut Steel meetings, Watertown Arsenal, Massachusetts, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Subcommittee for Aircraft Armor, reports and correspondence, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Subcommittee for Aircraft Armor, reports and correspondence [note: this folder contains fragile original documents. Please use the copies of these materials at the front of the folder.], 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to General Superintendent H.G. McIlvried regarding armor production and testing (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Reports from Metallurgical Department at Homestead Works, 1941-1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Reports from U.S. Steel Corporation of Delaware Research Lab, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Rolled Armour Subcommittee Report No. 48, "Study of 'Woody Fractures' in Rolled Armor Plate", January 17, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to and from F.T. Bumbaugh, Manager of Alloy Sales, re. Tank Armor Off Grade Analysis, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Metallurgy Tests, 1894 and 1912 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Open hearth data, armor heats, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Notes on lecture series, "Metallurgy of Iron and Steel", 1961 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Metallurgical Specification File Considerations," draft (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous metallurgical documents (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Computerized Control Systems, 1958-1983; III.
  The files in this series primarily illustrate the processes and decisions involved in implementing computer systems at the Homestead Works to track and chart progress in all areas of steel production and sales.
  - Computerization -- Homestead, 1.
    - "Structural Division Proposed Pre-Ramac Installation", 1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - "Proposal for Information and Control System", October 1966 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Systems Performance Specification, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Computer Installation and Operations, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Terminal Maintenance, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Plant Production Systems, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Plant Production Systems, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Presentation Introducing Electronic Data Processing Machines in Steel Management, ca. 1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Proposal for Homestead mechanical specification order processing system (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Computerized Production Reporting System, Forgings, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Handwritten Draft about OPD (Operating Practice Description) System, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - OPD (Operating Practice Description) Standard Practice, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - BOP (Basic Oxygen Process) Practice Sheet, Edgar Thomson Works, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Various Plant Operations Control Systems, 1973-1983 (Box 4, Folder 12-14)
    - Operating Practice Description, Back Up Information, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Control System -- Homestead, 2.
    - Annual Slab Inventory, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Operating Control System, Priority and Status Report, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Blue Prints/Flow Charts -- Structural Information and Control System (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Systems Activities (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Burrough Resident System Group -- Control Systems, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Objects, 3.
    - U.S.S. Hard Hat, 1981 (Box 35, Item 1)
    - Hard Hat, United States Conference of Mayors Visit to Pittsburgh, June 10, 1979 (Box 35, Item 2)
      Hard hat worn by William J. Gaughan during the United States Conference of Mayors Visit to Pittsburgh.
    - U.S.S. Banners (Box 36, Item 1-2)
    - U.S.S. Gold Cufflinks, 25 Years of Service (Box 37, Item 1-2)
    - U.S.S. Tie Clip, 25 Years of Service (Box 37, Item 3)
    - Silver Tie Clip, Big Shop Homestead Works (Box 37, Item 4)
    - Delegate Medal, District 15 Conference, April 29-30, 1960 (Box 37, Item 5)
    - Carnegie Steel Police Badge (Box 37, Item 6)
    - Carnegie 45 Steel Co. Badge (Box 37, Item 7)
    - Homestead Parking Token (Box 37, Item 8)
    - U.S.S. Zippo Lighter (Box 37, Item 9)
    - U.S.S. Employee ID Card (Box 37, Item 10)
      William J. Gaughan's employee ID card indicating his employment as part of the Metallurgical Department of the Homestead Works and his ability to access all parts of the Works.
    - Management Club Membership Card, Homestead Works (Box 37, Item 11)
    - Business Card Case (Box 37, Item 12)
      Business card case indicating William J. Gaughan's position of Senior Designer, Operations Planning and Control for the United States Steel Corporation, Homestead Works and personal cards used by Gaughan to represent his role of Consultant Lecturer Historian.
    - U.S.S. Pocket Knives, "The Big Shop" (Box 37, Item 13-14)
    - "Winjammer", U.S.S Corporation Homestead Works Management Club (Box 37, Item 15)
    - Ribbon, Retired Veteran Carnegie Steel Co. "Ye Olde Mills Outing", September 6, 1924 (Box 37, Item 16)
    - Employee Token (Box 37, Item 17)
      Employee token bearing the identification, "Homestead Steel Works Machine Shop No. 2 480" used to clock in and out for the work day.
    - Equipment Check Tag (Box 37, Item 18)
      Equipment check tag bearing the identification, "C.- I. S. Co.- HSTO Production Shops 138 Equipment Check".
    - Medallion, Fort Pitt Block House (Box 37, Item 19)
    - Medallion, 25 Years United States Steel Corp. (Box 37, Item 20)
    - Equipment Tag (Box 37, Item 21)
      Undated equipment tag bearing the identification, "U. S. Steel Co. HMSTD. ST. WKS. ELECT. SHOP Serial No. 693".
    - Employee Badges (Box 37, Item 22-25)
      Employee badges circa World War II. These include: one blue and green badge reading,"742 Defense Plant Homestead Carnegie- Illinois Steel Corporation Open Hearth Department"; one blue and silver badge reading "25468 Defense Plant Homestead Carnegie- Illinois Steel Corporation Trainee"; one red and white badge reading "Administrative 2137 Homestead District Works United States Steel Company"; one red and white badge reading,"Administrative 2628 Homestead Works United States Steel Company".
    - Button, The Big H Management Club (Box 38, Item 1-9)
    - Keychain, "I Belong to the Big Shop Team", USS Homestead Works (Box 38, Item 10)
    - Button, "There's no place like Homestead" (Box 38, Item 11)
    - Button, Carnegie Steel Co. "Ye Olde Mills Outing and Basket Picnic", September 6, 1924 (Box 38, Item 12)
    - Button, "Anything we can do we can do better" (Box 38, Item 13)
    - Button, VIP Visitor in Pennsylvania (Box 38, Item 14)
    - Button, "We Are Big Because We Are Involved" (Box 38, Item 15)
    - Token, "Elect 1397 Rank & File Candidates" (Box 38, Item 16)
    - Safety Glasses (Box 39, Item 1-2)
    - Universal English/Metric Converter Slide Rule
    - Metal Samples (Box 33-34)
- Steel Production and Plant Operations, 1935-1981; IV.
  This series contains items relating to the efficient and safe production of steel at the Homestead Works. Specific topics include basic and integral operations of the steel mill and the planning associated with maintaining high levels of production in the steel industry. Records in this series describe the production of various products including steel sheets, bearings, and beams and their sale. Also included is material relating to employee training and safety; items illustrating the effect of strikes on mill production; and the transfer of responsibility for effective mill operations from the accounting department to a specialized production-planning department in the 1950s.
  - Production -- General, 1.
    - "Bibliography of Sheet and Strip Mills for Committee on Construction," Homestead Works, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "Open Hearth Division: Man Turns per Week at Various Levels of Shop Activity", 1949 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Open Hearth Miscellaneous, 1949-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - "Product Facilities and Services, Johnstown Works, Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation", January 1950 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Management Roster, U.S. Steel Operation Department, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - "Production Planning Building, Air Raid Alert Procedure", 1955 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Papers of the Chief Metallurgist (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Production and Shipping Figures, 1964-1975 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Production Statistics, 1898-1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Structural Shorts, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Rough Draft, "Development of Process Sequence Operations Planning and Control Standard Practice", ca 1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Production Planning Department Papers (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Sales Orders, Mills, 1964 and 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Reports on Rolls and Bearings Mills, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Forge Rolls Information, ca. 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Study Relating to the Break-up Roll Breakage at 160" Plate Mill Homestead District Works", 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 160" Mill "Hot Rolled to Finish Yield" meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 160" Mill production statistics, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 160"/45" Mill Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Drafting Practices on 100" Mill, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 100" Mill Miscellaneous, 1948-1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Plate Mill Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Evaluation of Contoured Insulation Hot Top for 36" x 52" Beam Shape Mold (photographs included), August 20, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Training, 2.
    - "Open Hearth First Helper Training Program" for U.S. Steel Duquesne Works, October 12, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Furnace Operators manual" for Open Hearth at Edgar Thomson Works (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "Open Hearth Operating Experiences for Operating and Technical Trainees" (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Open Hearth #5 First helper Orientation program," Homestead Works, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - "First Helper's Manual," Open Hearth #5, Homestead Works, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Accounting, 3.
    - Report on "Proposed Transfer of Production Planning Responsibilities from the Accounting Department Mill Clerical Units to the Production Planning Department," Homestead Works, February 6, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Material Related to Proposed Transfer to Production Planning Responsibilities from the Accounting Department, 1952-1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Safety, 4.
    - Safety Supervisors Conference, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Safety Materials, 1957-1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Accident Report, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Emergency Operations Alerting Procedure (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Strikes -- Production Shutdown and Startup, 5.
    - Temporary Shutdown of Open Hearth #2, August 1945 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Start-up data for Open Hearth #2, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Four Day Open Hearth Division Operation Plan, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Shutdown data, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Open Hearth vacation analysis, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Employee Reallocation during Open Hearth #2 Shutdown, July 3, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Employee Reallocation during Open Hearth #3 Shutdown, July 3, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Employee Reallocation during Open Hearth #4 Shutdown, July 3, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Employee Reallocation during Open Hearth #5 Shutdown, July 3, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Shutdown Preparation for Strike, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Startup Operations for Strike, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 34)